跑什么啊  本渡
What's up, Hondo?
我没有把柄在你们手上
You guys got nothing on me.
-你杀了个警察  -口说无凭
- You killed a cop. - Allegedly.
你还到处炫耀
And then you bragged about it.
那你就逮捕我啊  美女
So arrest me, sweetheart.
你们那个黑鬼朋友的事
All right? You got nothing tying me
跟我扯不上关系
to that nigger friend of yours.
不信你们就尽管去查证
Okay, why don't you see if you can make it stick?
不  就是你杀了我们的朋友
No. You killed our friend.
我们不会逮捕你
We're not gonna arrest you.
你这话什么意思
What are you talkin' about?
你说得对  我们无法查证
You're right, we couldn't make it stick.
你们他妈不是警察吗  抓我啊
You're fucking cops, okay? Arrest me.
看到警徽了吗
See any badges?
你他妈可是警长啊
You're the fuckin' sheriff!
-口说无凭  -操...
- Allegedly. - Oh, fu...
《黑吃黑》第三季 第一集
Banshee S03E01
你想什么呢
Where do you go?
什么意思
What do you mean?
我是说
It's like...
你都不想看我
you can't even look at me.
不是那样的
It's nothing like that.
你真该考虑换个住处了
You know, maybe you should really think about getting a new place.
你不觉得这里有种老式的魅力吗
Eh, it has a certain old-school charm, no?
不觉得
No.
这里租金便宜啊
Well, you can't beat the rent.
我是说  就算只是床上关系
I mean, I get that this isn't a relationship,
我也可以接受
and I'm fine with that.
我得去工作了
I have to go to work.
你至少雇个人打扫打扫吧
You could at least hire a cleaning service or something.
我不喜欢别人碰我的东西
I don't like people touching my things.
-你的东西  -是啊
- Your things? - Yeah.
-这些东西不是你的  -别闹了  起床吧
- These aren't your things. - Okay, time to get up.
这里就是糖果的杂物间
This is where Sugar's old crap goes to die.
某人现在住房车里  还好意思这么说
Yeah, this coming from the girl who lives in an Airstream.
你看起来就像
You just seem like somebody
特别需要个朋友
who could use a friend is all I'm saying.
我们都是成年人  只是在汽车旅馆上床而已
We're just two adults having sex in a motel room.
算了  先不起床了
You know what? Fuck it.
过来
Come here.
你活儿很棒
Great sex.
还是有进步的空间
Always room for improvement.
-卡莉  来得真早啊  -睡不着
- Hey, Carrie, you're early. - I couldn't sleep.
点单
Order up.
班尼迪克蛋  少放沙司
Eggs Benedict, hold the sauce.
嘿  你们好啊
Man, you guys.
-你负责后面五张桌子好吗  -没问题
- Take the back five, okay? - You got it.
谁点了佛罗伦萨蛋
Who had an eggs Florentine?
吃鸡蛋吗
You want some eggs?
不了  谢谢
No, thanks.
听到了吗
You hear that?
什么
What?
安静
Quiet.
-你想贾伯了吗  -不是
- You missing Job? - No.
我只想说  自从你上个月从纽约回来
I'm just sayin' how nice and quiet it's been
我们的日子是多么静谧祥和啊
since you got back from your little trip to New York last month.
你不喜欢这样吗
You got a problem with quiet?
刚好相反
On the contrary.
静谧不再的时候我会想念的
I'm gonna miss it when it's gone.
怎么了
Yes?
关于我们讨论过的问题
In regards to the matter we discussed,
你应该去地下室一趟
you should come down to the basement.
-现在吗  -对
- Now? - Yes.
他准备开口了吗
Is he ready to talk?
看来你俩度过了一个愉快的夜晚
Looks like you two made quite a night of it.
我知道  我知道
I know, I know.
博登的问话风格有时候会很呆板
Burton's interview style can be a little rigid at times,
但是他一丝不苟
but he's very precise.
这些伤口会愈合的
These cuts will all heal.
前提是你能活到那个时候
You just make sure you live long enough to let that happen.
你明白吗  很好
Do you understand? Good.
吉姆·凯奇是不是一直给费城那边供货
Now, has Jim Cage been supplying Philadelphia with molly?
没错
Yeah.
而且他只卖给弗拉奇尔
And he's been selling to Frazier exclusively?
他们比你的价低
They cut your prices.
他已经控制了整个地区
He's got the whole territory locked up.
感谢你的合作
Thank you for your cooperation.
等等
Wait!
求你救救我
Please. Please help me.
求...
Pl--
我可不做这种事
That's not really my thing.
离我远点
Stay the fuck away from me!
水果拼盘  豆奶燕麦片
Fruit platter and oatmeal with soy milk.
还有蛋白卷饼
And an egg white omelet.
卡莉
Hi, Carrie.
你和孩子们怎么样了
How are you? How are the kids?
都很好  谢谢关心
Everyone's great. Thanks.
鸡蛋好了
Eggs over easy.
酥脆的培根也好了
Side of bacon, crisp.
谢谢
Thank you.
我很佩服她
I give her a lot of credit.
很不容易  对吧
It can't be easy, huh?
你还好吗
You okay?
没事
Yeah.
-普罗科特先生  -警长  副警长
- Mr. Proctor. - Sheriff, Deputy.
控告我持有非法武器
Charging me with unlicensed firearms.
你只能做到这种程度吗
That was the best you could do?
我要一直这么吊着你  直到找出证据控告你
Hust getting the ball rolling till I can charge you
-杀了朗西德  -你肯定能行
- with the Longshadow murder. - I'm sure you are,
不过多亏了你
but thanks to you
我才有完美的不在场证明  不是吗
I have an airtight alibi, don't I?
你把我关起来了  记得吗
You had me locked up, remember?
在我看来  对付你这样的人
The way I see it, a guy like you,
我还会有其它办法的
I'll get another shot.
不过你的业绩
Yeah, but your track record isn't exactly
让我不怎么担心
giving me much cause for concern.
再见  凯
See you around, Kai.
我每天来这里都想着会见到艾米特
I still come in every day expecting to see Emmett there.
我也是
Yeah, me, too.
早上好
Hey, morning.
-早上好  -瑞文
- Hey. - Raven.
我知道
Listen, I know that I...
我的前任工作很多  我得接替他
have some pretty big shoes to fill here.
-是超级多  -对对  我懂
- Huge. - Yeah, yeah, I get that.
但我整天就是接广告电话而已
But all I did was answer an ad.
真抱歉  对你来说肯定很不容易
I'm sorry. This can't be easy for you.
是不容易  但这能让我的家人离开居留地
It's not, but it gets my family off the reservation.
为宾州警察局干了六年之后
And I gotta tell you after working six years for KPD,
我很高兴能调到一个办实事的警察部门
it's great to be working in an actual functioning police station.
办实事  说的就是我们
Functional. That's us.
胡德  你有空吗
Hey, Hood, you got a minute?
怎么了
Yeah. What's up?
本渡的档案
Hondo file.
法医说他们不会派人去取
Medical examiner said they're not gonna send out
弹道痕迹检测结果
for ballistics on the bullets.
我想他们是优先处理了
They're prioritizing, I guess.
我检查了那片区域
And I, I canvassed the area.
看起来没人发现我们
No one seems to have seen anything.
基本上  官方一致认为
So, basically, the official consensus is
是三个无名持枪者清理了公害
three anonymous shooters did the world a favor
大家都可以睡个好觉
and nobody's gonna lose any sleep over
不用担心这个新纳粹分子出来捣鬼
a dead neo-Nazi with multiple priors.
-所以...  -我觉得挺好
- So... - Sounds good to me.
好的
OK.
还有事吗
Something else?
你就没有一点困扰吗
Are you even fazed by this?
我们处决了一个人  胡德
We executed a man, Hood.
他杀了我们的人
He killed one of us.
我知道
I know that.
我理解
I understand.
你以前干过这种事吗
You've done this sort of thing before?
什么事
What?
杀人吗
Killed a man?
不  行刑
No, executed him.
布罗克
Brock...
你会没事的
you'll be okay.
-出发吧  -别养成习惯了好吗  我...
- Now let's go. - Let's just not make a habit of it, okay? I...
父亲知道我们经常这样见面吗
Does Father know that we've been meeting like this?
问这个干嘛
To what end?
你知道他不会来的  对吗
You don't think he'll join us, do you?
但也许某一天他会想知道
But you would think at one point he'd want to know
他的儿子是怎样的人
what became of his son.
坦诚地说  凯
Let's be honest, Kai.
你现在的样子  正是他所惧怕的
Who you've become is exactly what he is afraid of.
我的外孙女怎么样
How is my granddaughter doing?
她很好
She's fine.
打他
Hit him!
烈火考验是红骨帮神圣的传统
The fire trials are a sacred Redbone tradition
以证明你有能力成为领导者
to prove yourself a worthy leader.
时代不同了
Times have changed
红骨帮必须与时俱进
and the Redbones must change with them.
不对
Wrong.
这里是警察局
Sheriff's Department.
比利  比利
Billy. Billy.
你得先按交接键
You have to press that interface button first
才能把电话从总机上转出来
in order to pull the call off Alma's switchboard.
-谢谢  -明白了吗
- Thanks. - Got it?
-是的  -熟能生巧  孩子
- Yeah. - Time and experience, son.
交接键
Interface.
-对了  -这里是警察局
- There you go. - Sheriff's Department.
洛特斯副警长刚刚出去了  有什么可以帮您的吗
Deputy Lotus stepped away for a moment. Can I help you?
现在你能看到他吗
Do you see him now?
所有门都关上了吗
Are all your doors locked?
你能再检查一遍吗
Can you check them for me, please?
告诉我你的地址
And tell me your address.
奥克伍德巷63号
知道了
Got it.
好的  我们马上出发  女士
Okay, we're on our way, ma'am.
好的  有人报警说有小偷
Okay, we got a prowler call.
有位女士说有人藏在她的灌木丛里
Lady said there's a guy hiding in her shrubbery,in her backyard.
是奥克伍德巷63号吗
Is it 63 Oakwood Lane?
是啊  你怎么知道
Yeah. How'd you know?
熟能生巧  孩子
Time and experience, son.
我去就行
I'll get it.
-我们一起去吧  -不  你待在这
- We should both go. - No, no, I need you to stay here
值班就好  好吗
and hold down the fort, all right?
时代没有改变
Times have not changed.
五百年来我们一直被那些白人
We are still being raped and plundered
蹂躏和掠夺
by the white man like we have been for 500 years.
我们有什么值得庆祝的
What exactly is it you think we're going to celebrate?
你已经离开了  谢顿  现在我说了算
You left, Chayton. I'm in charge.
-我知道  -真的吗
- I understand. - Do you?
我不想跟你打
I don't want to fight you.
我也不想跟你打
I don't want to fight you, either,
除非你有其他法子  否则这是必须的  谢顿
but that's how we do it unless you see another way, Chayton.
你可以直接认输
You could just step down.
你会认输吗
Would you?
-打够了吗  -够了  够了
- Had enough? - Yeah. Yeah.
-够了吗  -够了
- We done? - Yeah.
我们在这的  所有人
We are here, all of us,
去打一场永远也不会赢得战争
to fight in a war that we will never win
因为在百年之前我们就已经输了
because it was lost by our people centuries ago.
我们赢不回我们的国家
We will never reclaim our country.
但我已经回来了  因为我愿意誓死而战
But I've come back because I'd rather die fighting
也不愿像奴隶一样苟活于这片土地
than to live like a slave in my own land.
是时候开始反击了
It's time we took something back.
有人吗
Hello?
又是小偷
Another prowler, huh?
别再报假警了  艾米丽
Gotta stop it with these prowler calls, Emily.
好吗  如果比利·雷文接到电话时
All right? Look, what if I was out
我不在该怎么办
when Billy Raven took that call?
谁是比利·雷文
Who the hell's Billy Raven?
新警员
New deputy.
-可怜的埃米特  -我得回去了
- Poor Emmett. - I gotta get back.
先跟我喝一杯吧
Just have a drink with me.
-小艾  我还在值班呢  -你总在上班
- Em, I'm on duty. - You're always on duty.
所以我们才离婚了
That's why we got divorced.
我们离婚是因为你和艾略特·格兰杰搞上了
No, we got divorced because you were fucking Elliot Granger.
那是因为你总不在家
I was fucking Elliot Granger because you were never home.
到底是先有鸡还是先有蛋
Classic chicken and the egg debate.
和我坐会吧
Just sit with me.
拜托了
Please?
我只是有时候会寂寞
I just get lonely sometimes.
那就别一个人在晚上喝闷酒
Well, maybe you shouldn't drink alone at night.
问题解决
Done.
敬我们
To us.
好
Yeah.
最近如何  工作...
How's everything? How's-- how's work and--
你用不着和我寒暄
You don't have to make small talk with me.
别这样  快住手
Come on. Stop it.
别这样
Stop, stop.
该死的  小艾
Damn it, Em.
我只想确保你一切都好
I just wanted to make sure you were okay.
那就让我好起来吧
Then make me okay.
妈的
Damn it.
操我
Fuck me.
用力点
Harder.
疼吗
Did it hurt?
针头刚刺进去的时候特别疼
I mean, at first when they jab you with the needle it hurt a lot,
但是过一会儿你就习惯了
but, I don't know, after a while you just kind of get used to it.
就跟我的生活一样
Kind of like my life.
你爸找到新房子了吗
Did your dad find a new place yet?
嗯  他要租一个小破公寓
Yeah, he's renting this shitty little apartment.
真的挺烦人的
It's pretty depressing, actually.
你爸妈平时说话吗
He and your mom, like, talking?
偶尔吧
Sometimes, yeah.
一切都糟糕透顶
The whole thing is just so fucked up.
他们看到你的纹身都气疯了吧
I bet they freaked when they saw your tat.
他们都顾着纠结自己的破事
They're way too caught up in their own bullshit
哪里会注意我
to pay any attention to me.
我知道个地方能买到50刀的好啤酒
I know where we can get some premium bud for, like, 50 bucks.
-你有50刀吗  -没钱了
- You have 50 bucks? - Tapped out.
放屁  你老是没钱
No shit. You're always tapped out.
咬我啊
Bite me.
我有个主意
I have an idea.
我操
Holy shit.
瘾君子的玩具反斗城啊
It's like a stoner's Toys "R" Us.
全球最大的玩具及婴幼儿用品零售商
好了伙计们  该走了
All right, guys. Guys, come on.
走啊
Come on!
这是在深夜扫货吗
Doing a little late-night shopping?
你们两个  马上回家
You two, head home now.
这是最后一次警告
Consider this your last warning.
他开玩笑的吗
Is he joking?
你们两个  快走就是了
You guys, just-- just get out of here.
-你确定吗  -我没事  走吧
- Are you sure? - Yeah, I'm fine. Just go!
给我把东西放下
Hey! Leave the stuff.
这次又想做贼了  是吗
So, you wanna be a thief now?
给你点建议
A little piece of advice.
偷东西没你想的那么简单
It's harder than you think.
你的第一个错误  人太多
Your first mistake was your numbers.
多一个人  就多一分被抓的风险
Every extra person increases your chances of getting caught
你们三个人干一个人的活
and you had three people on a one-man job.
这不是个好开始
It's not a great start.
跟我来
Come with me.
看到门窗上的警报器了吗
You see an alarm on the door, window?
没有吗
Nope?
那我怎么这么快就来了呢
So how did I get here so fast?
看到上面那个白盒子了吗
See that little white box up there?
那是声音感测器
It's a sound sensor.
打碎玻璃  就会触发警报
You break the glass, that triggers a silent alarm.
十秒后  广播通知警局
10 seconds later, my office is on the radio,
我就来了
here I am.
碰到玻璃只能用切开的
Your only option with glass is a cutter.
这就是大奖了吧
So this is it, huh? Jackpot.
偷了多少
How much you got?
37块
37 dollars.
看  收银机也连着警报器
See, the register is also connected to the alarm.
所以你最好先搞定警报器
So you would've been better to take the whole thing
再撬开收银机
and open it when you got clear.
不过  如果真要存放一大笔钱过夜
Although, if there is any real cash left overnight...
那就肯定是存在保险柜里
it's gonna be in the safe,
当然也已经牢牢固定在地板上了
which is also bolted to the floor.
除非你知道怎么破开保险箱
So unless you know how to crack a safe...
不知道吗
No?
那就真没被盗走多少钱
Well, then there's really nothing in here
也就没必要逮捕你了
worth getting arrested for.
除非  你想要这样
Unless, of course, that was the point.
你觉得我想被抓吗
You think I wanted to get caught?
咱家人都有作死基因呗
Self-destruction runs in the family.
我不觉得现在就可以开这种父女玩笑
A little soon to be making daddy jokes, don't you think?
我就试试
You never know until you try.
扬恩斯
愿你安详
To your health.
不知道你最近怎么样  但是
I don't know what you've been up to, but, uh...
我刚和我前妻来了一炮
I just had sex with my ex-wife.
又是这样
Again.
我懂我懂我懂
I know, I know, I know.
我知道你想说什么
But you know what? I know what you're gonna say
但是你从没离过婚  所以
and you've never been divorced, so...
我想告诉你的是
Hey, look, I wanted to tell you...
我们整垮本渡了
we took care of Hondo.
他害死了你  我们让他罪有应得了
Oh, man, we made him pay for what he did to you.
我猜你俩能在那边碰到
I doubt you'll be running in the same circles up there
说不定不能  但是
or wherever, but...
如果你要是遇到他  记得是我们干的
if you happen to run into him, that was us.
我知道你肯定又要扯圣经里的话
I know, I know, you probably have some Bible verse
什么上帝会惩戒恶人之类的
about leaving revenge to God,
但是埃米特  有的时候你等不到上帝
but, you see, Emmett, sometimes you cannot wait
让全世界和平相处  因为在你等的时候
for God to put the world to right because while you're waiting,
世界只会继续暴乱不堪
the world just keeps going to shit.
现在  胡德是我们的头
And when you have a guy like Hood leading the charge,
上帝如果还想继续管
well, God's just gonna have to move a lot faster
那就让祂快点  这话我撂在这
if He wants to keep up and you can tell Him I said that.
我想你了
I miss you.
干杯
Cheers.
你来干什么
What are you doing here?
我想来看看孩子  却发现他们独自在家
I stopped by to see the kids, found them here alone,
所以我决定留下来陪他们吃晚饭
so I decided to stay and have dinner with them.
-蒂法呢  -她早就上床睡觉了  卡莉
- Where's Deva? - She went to bed hours ago, Carrie.
-现在都过零点了  -我得通宵加班
- It's past midnight. - I had to work late.
我有时候觉得你根本就没在餐馆里上班
You know, somehow I don't think you were at the diner.
许多单身母亲都得打两份工
Well, you know, a lot of single mothers have to work two jobs.
别这样了
This has to stop.
咱别吵
Let's not do this.
离婚不就是为了不会再吵架了吗
Isn't the whole point of getting a divorce so we don't have to fight?
难道你没发现
How can you not realize that
你没法给孩子们幸福吗
you are risking the well-being of your children?
你怎么回事  嗑药了么
What is it with you? Some sort of addiction or something?
你自己清楚
You would know.
对不起
I'm sorry.
所以你和妈不会复合了
So you and Mom way back when.
-对  -以后也不可能吗
- Yeah. - But not anymore?
-是  -你怎么忍心离开她
- No. - How come you left her?
她当时可是怀孕了
I mean, she was pregnant.
她早该去找你
She should have found you.
-早该和你说  -不不
- She should have told you. - No, no.
不是她的错
It wasn't her fault.
她不可能不顾自己和你的生命
There was no way she could have got to me
一定要和我在一起
without putting herself, and you, in a lot of danger.
后来她遇到了你爸
Then after she met your father,
她所做的事全都是为了你好
she did what was best for you.
我想说的是
The point is
你才应该和你妈重归于好
why don't you take it easy on your mom?
她打我生下来就在骗我
She lied to me my whole life.
不  她是想保你安全
No, she tried to keep you safe.
她抛下了一切  她这一辈子
She left everything. Her whole life.
她放弃了一切
Gave it all up. Everything.
她都是为了你
She did that for you.
你什么时候知道我的事的
When did you know about me?
第一次见到你的时候
The first time I saw you.
你是为她来的吗
You came here for her?
但我是为你而留下来的
But I stayed for you.
-爸爸  -我看你不是上床了吗
- Hi, Dad. - Hey, I saw you go to bed.
-又醒了呗  -蒂法
- Woke up. - Deva?
-这样不好  -随你怎么说
- This is not okay. - Yeah, tell me about it.
你在哪找到她的
Where'd you find her?
她只是和别的孩子一起在外面玩
She was just out with some other kids.
好吧  谢谢你把她带回来
Yeah, well, thanks for bringing her back.
没事  晚安
Yeah. Have a good night.
胡德
Hood.
卡莉说过要对我坦白一切
You know, Carrie promised to tell me everything,
但一旦涉及到你...
but when it came to you...
她就什么都不说
nothin'.
不管你的秘密是什么
Whatever your secrets are,
都值得让她不惜对自己的丈夫说谎
they were worth breaking a promise to her husband.
你毁了我的婚姻
You ended my marriage. Please...
求你不要再缠着我的女儿了
leave me my daughter.
我不管是谁让她这样的
I don't care who made her.
我是她...
I'm her--
我是她父亲
I'm her father.
我求你了
I'm asking you, please.
萨瓦脱衣舞俱乐部
这是我们昨天晚上拍下来的
This is what we took in last night.
你点这里就能看到上礼拜的
And if you click here, you can see the same day last week,
上个月的  还有去年的
last month, and last year.
你点这里
You click here,
你就能看到每个姑娘带进去的东西
you can see what each girl is bringing in.
-好的  -我觉得今晚就先到这里吧
- Okay. - Anyway, I think this is enough for tonight.
你要不去俱乐部里看看
Why don't you check on the club?
我还要在这处理些事情
I'll finish up a few things here.
普罗科特盯上了朗西德的东西
Proctor had his hands in Longshadow's pockets.
一报还一报
One thing leads to another.
现在郎西德死了
Now Longshadow is dead.
我们要来找你了  白妞
We'll be coming for you, white girl.
找你...
You...
还有普罗科特
and Proctor.
马上
Soon.
快点  快点  我们走
Come on, come on. Let's go!
那是谁
Who the hell is that?
这是美国海军陆战队的车
This is a United States Marine Corps vehicle.
请让开
Step aside--
联络中心  这里是K19
TOC, kilo-one-niner.
庞德菲尔德15号街遭遇敌袭
Taking hostile contact on Pondfield 15.
-请求...  -我们没时间等增援了
- Requesting-- - We don't have time to wait for backup.
让我们出去
Get us out of here.
操他妈的
Motherfuckers.
刚接到报告  庞德菲尔德发生交火
Just got a report of shots being fired on Pondfield Road.
庞德菲尔德  那就在热那亚营附近
Pondfield Road, that's near Camp Genoa.
-可能正在训练  -不可能没通知我们
- Could be running exercises. - Not without notifying us.
西沃恩  我们就在附近  马上到
Siobhan, we're close by. We're on it.
杰克逊  你没事吧
Jackson, you okay?
杰克逊  回答我
Jackson, answer--
干掉他了
Got him.
快点  我们走
Come on, let's go!
开车  开车
Move it, move it!
阿尔玛  我们需要支援
Alma, we need backup!
急救中心  这里有多人伤亡
EMS, we got multiple casualties!
重复  多人伤亡
Repeat, multiple casualties!
在担心那个印第安人吗
Are you worried about the Indian?
他早就知道
He knew.
他怎么会知道
How could he know?
他们当然会怀疑和我有关
They would naturally suspect my involvement.
谁挑起的对他们来说不重要
Who pulled the trigger is not important to them.
看来对他来说很重要
It seemed pretty important to him.
我会给这里安排个保镖
You know, I'm gonna put a guard in the house.
不管你去哪  博登都跟着你
Anywhere you go, Burton will go with you.
那个印第安人不会再靠近你了
That Indian won't get near you again.
-早  警长  -早
- Morning, Sheriff. - Morning.
您需要什么帮助  长官
How can I help you, sir?
谁是这里的负责人
Who's the CO here?
斯托上校  长官
Colonel Stowe, sir.
好吧  我要见他
Okay, well, I need to see him.
你有预约吗
You have an appointment to see the colonel?
你刚告诉我他的名字  怎么会有预约
You just told me his name. How could I have an appointment?
没有许可不能进
No one gets on base without authorization.
今天早些时候有四名陆战队员
There were four Marines killed on the road earlier today,
在离此八英里的路上被杀
about eight miles from here.
-你肯定听说了  -是的  长官
- I'm sure you heard about it. - Yes, sir.
这是一起凶杀案调查
Well, this is a homicide investigation.
这就是我的许可
That's my authorization.
-胡德警长  -斯托上校
- Sheriff Hood. - Colonel Stowe.
我正等你呢
I've been expecting you.
你的门卫可不是这么说的
Not according to your men at the gate.
他们只是遵守规定而已
They were just following protocol.
这边走
This way.
上校
Hey, Colonel.
我想先告诉你我有多遗憾
Let me just start by saying how sorry I am.
这是场悲剧
It's a tragedy.
加在一起他们在伊拉克和阿富汗
Nine tours in Iraq and Afghanistan
出生入死了九回
between 'em,
却在宾州女妖镇的旧基地
and they get killed
演练时被杀了
demilling an antiquated base in Banshee, Pennsylvania.
我都不知道怎么告诉他们的家人
I have no idea how I'm gonna talk their families through that one.
道格拉斯·斯托上校
Colonel Douglas Stowe.
你们要关闭这里吗
So you're shutting the place down?
我们只是把这里清理出来
We're basically clearing house for all the contraband
好存放从战区运来的非法走私品
that gets shipped out of the war zones.
枪支  贵重物品  毒品  什么都有
Guns, valuables, drugs, you name it.
还有现金
And cash.
你们纳税人的钱
Your tax dollars at work.
有的用来从街头买枪
Whether we're buying guns off the streets
以保护他们免受塔利班的侵害
to keep them from the Taliban
有的就装在文件箱里拿给士兵们
or sending out soldiers with briefcases full of money
去买通线人
to pay off informants.
我们有一半的阿富汗人要养
We've got half of Afghanistan on the damn payroll.
我们用不掉的钱需要清点记录
The money we don't use has to be inventoried
送回美联储以备下次战争使用
and sent back to the Fed to be wasted in the next war.
好吧  但你不赞成
Right. You don't agree?
我不喜欢战争
I don't like war.
但是当战斗需要我
But when you ask me to fight,
我就战斗
let me fight.
那四名被杀的陆战队员
So the four Marines who were killed,
他们是在运送现金吗
they were transporting cash?
不是  我们不用卡车运现金
No, we don't move cash in trucks.
我们会安排装甲车运
We contract armored vehicles for that.
那些大部分是充公的自动武器
Those were mostly confiscated automatic weapons.
要运去联邦机构销毁的AK47和M4
AKs and M4s headed to a Fed facility to be destroyed.
所以现在红骨帮武装得和塔利班一样了
Great, so now the Redbones are armed like the Taliban.
你说什么  红骨帮
I'm sorry, the Redbones?
那些劫了你们卡车的人
The guys who jacked your truck.
他们是居留地的一个部落帮派
They're a tribal gang from the reservation.
你有箱子里装的那些东西的清单吗
Do you have a list of everything that was in those crates?
-我有  -太好了  如果你可以
- I do. - Great, well, if you could
让人帮我把它打印出来...
just have one of your people print that out for me, then...
胡德警长  很高兴你能来
Sheriff Hood, I appreciate the visit
也感谢你和你的下属
and the fact that you and your deputies
尽全力阻止他们
tried your best to stop these people.
不过他们杀了我的海军陆战队员
But the moment they killed my Marines
还偷了政府财产
and stole government property,
那就变成军事问题了
this became a matter for the military.
联调局和印第安人事务局
NCIS will lead the investigation with
会和海军调查处协调调查的
the FBI and the BIA.
会有很多文件要处理
Now, that's a lot of fuckin' letters,
你绝对不想
and the last thing you want
掺和进来的
is be getting caught up in the middle of it.
没错  但他们可能会持枪到我的镇上来
That's true, but those guns may end up on the streets of my town.
如果真去了  那你请随意反击
And if they do, you feel free to shoot back.
我们这死了四个人
We got four dead Marines here.
没有人想跟一个自以为是的警长
No one's gonna have the patience for a small-town sheriff
浪费时间
who thinks he knows better.
好吧
Okay.
-那打扰了  -墨菲上校会送你出去
- Thanks for your time. - Captain Murphy here will show you out.
谢谢你的来访
Thanks again for coming by.
你看起来不像海军啊  墨菲上校
You don't look like a Marine, Captain Murphy.
我是糖果
Sugar here.
还记得我们一直在找的大单子吗
You know that one big job we've been looking for?
我想我找到了
Well, I think I found it.
-说说看  -在海军基地  热那亚基地
- Do tell. - The Marine base, Camp Genoa.
他们用货车运现金
They're moving cash by the truckload.
好几百万
Millions of dollars.
如果在运钱  那说明他们仍配有
If they're moving that kind of money, they're still gonna have
军用级别的安全系统
military grade security systems.
是啊  不过咱可认识人
Yeah, if only we knew someone
能黑进他们的军用网络
who could hack into the military network.
已经过了25分钟了
It's been 25 minutes.
你应该黑进去了
You should be in by now.
你要是被枪指着看你怎么快得起来
You try working with a motherfuckin' hand cannon in your face.
这里可是纽约证券交易所
This here is the New York Stock Exchange.
有很多运行程序
There's a lot of moving parts.
那你让它们运行的快点啊
Well, then, make them move a little bit faster.
技术讲究的不是黑进去
The trick ain't gettin' in.
而是在神不知鬼不觉中
The trick is gettin' out
已经结束了任务
without anyone knowing you've been there.
我对这些没兴趣
That's of no concern to me.
-好了  -搞定了  进去了吗
- There. - That's it? You're in?
不  不是  只是个信号
Oh, no, that's just the signal.
信号  什么信号
Signal? What signal?
我操  他把钱拿走了
Damn it, he got the fuckin' money!
去追啊
Go get him.
-你看我跑得动么  -见鬼
- Have you seen me run? - Bullshit!
玩脱了
Bollocks.
我操
Fuck me!
电话来的真不是时候
Now is not really a good time.
没事吧  事情办得怎么样了
Everything okay? How'd the Fat Al thing go?
全被烧了
Up in fuckin' smoke.
我真的都开始信上帝了
You know, I'm actually starting to believe in God?
而且我觉得那王八蛋不怎么喜欢我
And I'm thinkin' that motherfucker hates me.
是的  说个好消息让你高兴一下
Yeah, well, I got something might cheer you up.
那可不见得
I highly doubt that.
这他妈什么情况  贾伯
What the fuck, Job?
等等
Hold on.
-这是所有的钱吗  -那个傻逼把自己炸死了
- Is this all the money? - Motherfucker sat on his own grenade!
我去
Damn.
我不会回宾夕法尼亚了
I ain't coming back to Pennsylvania.
我刚看到800万到1000万的脏钱
I just had eyes on eight to ten million in unwashed U.S. Dollars.
你真烦
I hate you.
知道吗  你真是讨厌死了
You know that? I fuckin' hate you.
迈尔斯餐厅
你要服务"鸭子王朝"那帮人了
I see you met the "Duck Dynasty" Guys.
是啊
Yeah.
别担心  等他们走了我会给座位消毒的
Don't worry, I'll sanitize the booth when they leave.
这是你们的
Here you go.
你们想吃点什么
What can I get you guys to eat?
一份豪华汉堡和你的电话号码怎么样
How about a deluxe burger and your phone number?
-我没有手机  -没事
- I don't have a phone. - That's all right.
我们也不需要聊天
We don't have to talk.
你会想把手拿开的
You're gonna want to move that hand.
-舒服吗  -耶
- How's that? - Yeah.
-你觉得爽吗  -当然了
- Does that feel good? - Sure does.
是吗
Yeah?
-希望你觉得值得  -什么值得
- Hope it was worth it. - Worth what?
汉堡要几成熟
How do you want that burger cooked?
嗨
Hi.
发生了什么
So what happened?
-他摸了我的屁股  -那你就打断了他的鼻子
- He grabbed my ass. - So you broke his nose?
你真得觉得自己适合来教育我吗
Do you really think you're the right person to be lecturing me?
是的  因为我是你现在唯一的朋友
Yeah, 'cause right now I'm the only friend you've got.
所以我要再问你一次
So I'll ask you one more time.
你怎么了
What's going on with you?
我他妈现在在做服务员
I'm a fucking waitress.
离婚了  孩子们
I'm getting divorced and my kids look at me
也不认我了
like they don't know me anymore.
还被近亲繁殖的傻逼乱摸
And I'm getting groped by inbred freaks.
他妈的看看我现在
Fucking look at me.
回家吧
Go home.
我来搞定
I'll clean this up.
那么就是它了
So this is the one, huh?
是的
Yeah.
我也不清楚
I don't know.
一个军事基地
A military base.
听起来挺危险的
Sounds risky.
高风险高回报
Anything worthwhile usually is.
而且它已经停止使用了
And it's being decommissioned.
贾伯怎么说
What about Job?
他说他会考虑的
He said he'd think about it.
我觉得他不会回来了
I don't think he's coming back here.
看看你  糖果
Look at you, Sugar,
已经在试着排挤我了
already trying to cut me out.
那是你开车时的打扮吗
Is that your driving outfit?
是的
Yes, it is.
而且幸运的是它也是"别惹我"的打扮
And fortunately it's also my "Don't take any shit" outfit.
所以不管你想要说什么
So whatever it is you thinking about sayin',
咽下去再给我倒杯他妈的威士忌
swallow it and pour me a fuckin' whiskey.
如果我现在就开始喝了
If I start drinkin' now,
也许我会醉到可以在白天面对这镇子了
maybe I'll be drunk enough to handle this town in daylight.
先生们
Gentlemen...
敬热那亚基地
Camp Genoa.
在我来这里的路上
You know, my whole way over here,
我一直在想
I just kept thinking,
我不敢相信我会回到这个狗屁地方
"I can't believe I'm coming back to this shithole
和他妈的海军陆战队交手
to mix it up with the fuckin' Marines."
我担心的不是海军陆战队
Well, it's not the Marines I'm worried about.
-我担心的是赏金猎人  -赏金猎人
- It's the mercs. - The mercs?
你他妈跟本就没说这事
You didn't say nothing about no motherfuck--
什么样的赏金猎人
what kind of mercs?
很坏的那种
Well, the bad kind.
如果要我猜的话应该是前海豹突击队的
I'd say ex-Navy SEALs if I had to guess.
我才不信这狗屁呢
I don't believe this shit.
你怎么了
What is it with you?
你想找死吗  是这样吗
Is it a death wish? Is that what it is?
如果是这样
Because if it is,
你干嘛不自己出去然后自杀呢
why don't you go out and get yourself killed?
你为什么老让我和你一起送命
Why do you always want to get me killed with you?
-很多钱的  -对手是他妈的全副武装的士兵
- It's a lot of money. - It's fucking soldiers with guns.
他妈的重型武器  我们不是在说保镖
Big fucking guns. We ain't talking about rent-a-cops.
也不是在说警察
We ain't even talkin' about real cops.
我们谈论的是他妈的突击队
We talkin' about fuckin' commandos.
-他们不会发现  -打住
- They'll never see us com-- - Uh-uh, nope!
还是说说钱的事儿吧
Tell me about the money.